

- kaleb22@hotmail.com
- Santo Andre, SP
- www.linkedin.com/in/kalebdalla
- □ Brazilian
- 11989796023

About me

You can find my portfolio here: portfolio

Summary

I have more than 5 years of experience developing web applications. Part of this period I have worked as a full stack developer. Right now I'm more focused in front-end development.

Medium Articles

RxJs - two data retrieve patterns for you to use

RxJS — Why should you learn it?

An intro to the Angular framework. Key concepts explained

How to test a component that uses activatedRoute class in Angular?

CSR vs SSR. Which one is the best?

how to dockerize a react back-end app and postgres

Current Tech Stack

Angular

Java / Spring Boot

AWS services

Github

Postman

Languages

Portuguese

English

Certifications

CAF

Cambridge Advanced English

Kaleb Dalla Pria

Senior Software Engineer

Lifelong learning:)

Work experience

Senior Software Engineer

Since January 2022 Itau Unibanco São Paulo, Brazil

My current position is focused in building web applications using Angular2+ with a microfrontend architecture for Itau's internet banking.

Software Engineer / Tech Lead

From May 2020 to December 2021 Itau Unibanco São Paulo, Brazil

As a tech lead I was responsible for giving support to other team members (mobile and web devs), designing technical solutions and planning new features.

Software Engineer

From January 2018 to May 2020 Itau Unibanco São Paulo, Brazil

Develop web applications for Itau's internet banking. I Worked as a full stack developer using mainlyn Java/SpringBoot to build BFFs, JavaScript, Jquery and AngularJs in the front-end.

Intern

From December 2016 to December 2017 Itau Unibanco São Paulo, Brazil Assist in the development of web applications for Itau's internet banking.

Summer Internship

From June 2016 to August 2016 University of Southern California Los Angeles, United States

Assist the team of DeterLab in the area of network infrastructure.

Education

Computer Science

From June 2013 to May 2021 Universidade Federal do ABC Santo André, Brazil

Science and Technology

From May 2013 to January 2018 Universidade Federal do ABC Santo André, Brazil

Scholarship

From June 2015 to May 2016 Florida State University Tallahassee, United States Science Without Boarders - I studied two semesters of computer science at FSU

Skills

JavaScript

I have experience working with JavaScript and jQuery.

Angular

I'm currently working with this framework.

TypeScript

Java / Spring Boot

I have experience developing back-end for front-end applications with Java/Sping.

AngularJs

I worked in several projects using this framework.

Additional education

The Complete Web Developer in 2022

Since June 2022 Zero to Mastery Udemy

Complete Angular Developer in 2022

From March 2022 to May 2022 Zero to Mastery Udemy

The Complete Junior to Senior Web Development RoadMap

From January 2020 to March 2020 Zero to Mastery Udemy